metrixstream.com 2014-04-09

# Online Video Platform | Live Video Streaming Software | Metrixstream

MetrixApps privacy policy covers the collection and use of personal information that may be collected by MetrixApps Software anytime you interact with MetrixApps Software such as when you license an MetrixApps Software product, contact a technical support or sales associate, sign up for an e-newsletter or request a download of demonstration software.

We collect your personal information because it assists us in delivering a high level of customer service. For example, your personal information helps us to keep you informed and up-to-date on the latest product updates and announcements as well as special offers that may be extended from time to time.

When you provide MetrixApps with your name, email address, mailing address or telephone number, and you do not "opt-out", MetrixApps Software and MetrixApps Software representatives and authorized affiliates may use the provided information to alert you to product updates, special offers, updated information, new products and other MetrixApps Software information. Other than MetrixApps Software representatives and authorized affiliates (such as value-added resellers), MetrixApps Software does not offer, sell, or otherwise make available any user-provided information to third parties.

MetrixApps will send notifications regarding product updates and technical support notices. These messages are deemed essential to the functionality of your product and as such, there is no "opt-out" available for update notifications.

If you do not want MetrixApps Software or MetrixApps Software representatives to contact you, you may "opt- out" at any time. You may "opt-out" by contacting MetrixApps Software's Customer Service Department or by following the instructions included in the email correspondence.

### Our Web Site and Cookies

MetrixApps Software's website utilizes visitor log files or cookies as well as hosted tracking with our website. The information collected with visitor cookies and through the hosted tracking is used to gain a better understanding of which sections of our site are most important to our users as well as identify possible navigation issues. This allows us to enhance your user experience in the future. The data collected from these visitor cookies and hosted tracking does not collect any personally identifiable information and is used in aggregate form only.

### Protecting Your Personal Information

Where personal information is required, the MetrixApps website uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption to transmit this data. This is done to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of the information you have offered. While MetrixApps strives to protect the personal information you submit to us, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. As such, MetrixApps cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our from our products and you do so at your own risk. Once your information has been received by MetrixApps, we will make our best effort to ensure the safety and security on our systems.

At times, MetrixApps may hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf. Such limited services include, but are not limited to, order fulfillment, direct mail services and answering customer questions about products and services. These companies will only be provided the information they need to perform the service, and they are strictly prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

MetrixApps may occasionally present a special contest or promotion sponsored by another company. You may be asked to provide personal information in order to quality for this contest or promotion. If your personal information will be shared with the sponsor(s), you will be notified prior to your submission of personal information.

Finally, while we will make every effort to preserve the privacy of our users, at times we may be required by law to disclose personal information.
